It's feeding time.
Killer Whale is a thriller, horror, action film directed by Jo-Anne Brechin.
Follows best friends Maddie and Trish as they find themselves trapped in a
remote lagoon with the dangerous killer whale named Ceto.
Maddie, played by Virginia Gardner.
Trish, played by Melanie Jarnson.
Josh, played by Mitchell Hope.
Chad, played by Isaac Crawley.
Hooded Man, played by Scott James George.
Waiter, played by Luke Cunningham.
Killer Whale is a 2026 survival thriller film directed by Jo-Anne
Brechin and written by Brechin and Katharine McPhee.
The film stars Virginia Gardner, Mel Jarnson, and Mitchell Hope.
The plot follows two best friends who find themselves
trapped in a remote lagoon with a vengeful orca.
The film was released theatrically in the United
States by Lionsgate on January 16, 2026.
The film explores themes of biting, survival horror,
killer whale, orca, aquatic horror.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and thought_provoking.